export default {
  name: "Spanish Words: House",
  cards: [
  { front: "table", back: "(la) mesa" },
  { front: "kitchen", back: "(la) cocina" },
  { front: "door", back: "(la) puerta" },
  { front: "glass", back: "(el) vaso" },
  { front: "mirror", back: "(el) espejo" },
  { front: "wooden spoon", back: "(la) cuchara de madera" },
  { front: "plate", back: "(el) plato" },
  { front: "bathroom", back: "(el) baño" },
  { front: "fork", back: "(el) tenedor" },
  { front: "light bulb", back: "(la) bombilla" },
  { front: "bookshelf", back: "(el) estante para libros" },
  { front: "attic", back: "(el) ático" },
  { front: "wall", back: "(la) pared" },
  { front: "soap", back: "(el) jabón" },
  { front: "bedroom", back: "(el) dormitorio" },
  { front: "mattress", back: "(el) colchón" },
  { front: "bowl", back: "(el) cuenco" },
  { front: "mailbox (for letters)", back: "(el) buzón" },
  { front: "cutlery", back: "(los) cubiertos" },
  { front: "chair", back: "(la) silla" },
  { front: "scale", back: "(la) báscula" },
  { front: "wardrobe", back: "(el) armario" },
  { front: "stairs", back: "(la) escalera" },
  { front: "laundry basket", back: "(la) cesta de la ropa" },
  { front: "pan", back: "(la) sartén" },
  { front: "drawer", back: "(el) cajón" },
  { front: "basement", back: "(el) sótano" },
  { front: "basin", back: "(el) lavabo" },
  { front: "cup (for hot drinks)", back: "(la) taza" },
  { front: "blanket", back: "(la) manta" },
  { front: "knife", back: "(el) cuchillo" },
  { front: "neighbour", back: "(el) vecino" },
  { front: "towel", back: "(la) toalla" },
  { front: "ladle", back: "(el) cucharón" },
  { front: "desk", back: "(el) escritorio" },
  { front: "roof", back: "(el) techo" },
  { front: "shelf", back: "(el) estante" },
  { front: "clock", back: "(el) reloj" },
  { front: "bathtub", back: "(la) bañera" },
  { front: "sofa", back: "(el) sofá" },
  { front: "curtain", back: "(la) cortina" },
  { front: "garden", back: "(el) jardín" },
  { front: "toilet paper", back: "(el) papel higiénico" },
  { front: "bath towel", back: "(la) toalla de baño" },
  { front: "window (building)", back: "(la) ventana" },
  { front: "pot", back: "(la) olla" },
  { front: "shower", back: "(la) ducha" },
  { front: "broom", back: "(la) escoba" },
  { front: "chopstick", back: "(el) palillo" },
  { front: "balcony", back: "(el) balcón" },
  { front: "spoon", back: "(la) cuchara" },
  { front: "bucket", back: "(el) balde" },
  { front: "pillow", back: "(la) almohada" },
  { front: "garage", back: "(el) garaje" },
  { front: "elevator", back: "(el) ascensor" },
  { front: "living room", back: "(la) sala de estar" },
  { front: "garbage bin", back: "(el) cubo de basura" },
  { front: "chimney", back: "(la) chimenea" },
  { front: "toilet (at home)", back: "(el) inodoro" },
  { front: "fence", back: "(la) valla" },
  { front: "picture", back: "(el) cuadro" },
  { front: "bed", back: "(la) cama" },
  { front: "ladder", back: "(la) escalera" },
  { front: "cup (for cold drinks)", back: "(el) vaso" },
  ],
};
